Finding Aid for the Stanley F. Pamphlet Horn Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Lockett, William C. From Nashville Back to Nashville, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- The Last Account of the Battle of Corinth, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Lucas, Dorothy Culbert. The Story of Jane and William Culbert, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- McAlister, J.M. A Rebel Yell, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- McArone. The Life and Adventures of Jeff Davis, 1865 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- McCabe, W. Gordon. Captain Robert E. Lee, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- McCabe, W. Gordon. Speech Delivered Before the New England Society, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- McCall, William A. Cherokees and Pioneers, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- McCallam, James. A Brief Sketch of the Settlement and Early History of Giles County, Tennessee, 1876 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- McCollam, James, and Campbell, J.P. Rev. The Cumberland Harmony---A Choice Collection of Psalm Tunes, Hymns, Songs, and Anthems, 1834 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- McClary, Ben Harris, ed. The Lovingood Papers, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- McClary, Ben Harris, ed. The Lovingood Papers, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- McDonald, Hunter. General Robert E. Lee After Appomattox, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- McEwen, John A. An Address Delivered at the Laying of the Cornerstone of the University of Nashville, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- McGovern, James R. Andrew Jackson and Pensacola, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- McKane, Elizabeth. The Story of Robert E. Lee, 1905 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- McKim, Randolph Harrison. The Motives and Aims of the Soldiers of the South in the Civil War, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- McManaway, James G. The Authorship of Shakespeare, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- McNeilly, James H. The Failure of the Confederacy---Was It a Blessing?, 1911(?). (Box 12, Folder 7)
- McVoy, Lizzie Carter, and Campbell, Ruth Bates. A Bibliography of Fiction by Louisianians and on Louisiana Subjects, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Malone, Dumas. The Pen of Douglas Southall Freeman, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Manlove, W. R. Kunjur Tales and Oddments, 1930 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Manufacturing and Mercantile Resources of Nashville, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Marshall, Charles. Address Delivered Before the Lee Monument Association, Oct. 27, 1887, 1888; (2 copies) (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Marshall Field and Co. Books, 1941-1942, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Martin, Josephine Bacon. Midway Georgia in History and Legend, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Martin, Thomas W. Horseshoe Bend National Military Park, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Martin, Thomas W., et al. National Significance of the Battle of Horseshoe Bend, Alabama, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Mason, John B. A Brochure on the Fourteenth Amendment, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Mayo, Robert. The Affidavit of Andrew Jackson, 1840 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Meuse, William. The Weapons of the Battle of New Orleans, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Middleton, Arthur Pierce, and Adair, Douglas. The Mystery of the Horn Papers, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- The Military Campaign of Nathan Bedford Forrest (Historical Map), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Military Operations of the Civil War, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- The Militia Law of the State of Tennessee, 1840 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Miller, C.A. Johnsoniana, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Miller, C.A. Sir John Hawkins, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Miller, Harriet Park. The Bell Witch of Middle Tennessee, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Miller, Stephen Franks. Ahab Lincoln, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Monaghan, Jay. Swamp Fox of the Confederacy: The Life and Military Services of M. Jeff Thompson, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Montgomery, Horace. Johnny Cobb: Confederate Aristocrat, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Monticello, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Moody, Charles N., et al. Soil Survey of Sumner County, Tennessee, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Moody, D.W. The Life of a Rover, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Moore, John Trotwood. Tom’s Last Forage, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Morgan, Marshall. The Battle of Franklin, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Morgan, Marshall. Tennessee Town, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Morrison, John, and Hamsley, Bob. The Real David Crockett, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Mosby, C.V. A Little Journey to the Home of Andrew Jackson, 1922; (2 copies) (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Moss, Charles. Forgotten Fort Heiman, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Nashville Centennial Trade Guide and Business Directory, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Nashville Chamber of Commerce. Nashville, Tennessee, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Nashville Chamber of Commerce. Nashville, Tennessee, ca., 1932 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Nashville Chamber of Commerce. Nashville, Tennessee---The Athens of the South, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Nashville Chamber of Commerce. Progress Nashville, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Nashville City Guide, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Nashville---Illustrated in Color, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Nashville and Tennessee Centennial and International Exposition, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Newton, A. Edward. Men and Ghosts of Gough Square, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- A North American. To General Lafayette, 1831. (From Andrew Jackson’s White House library, with note in his handwriting) (Box 14, Folder 10)
- A Northern Man. Curiosity Visits to Southern Plantations, 1863 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- An Officer in the Service of Walker. The Destiny of, 1856 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Official Record from the War Department. Proceedings of the Court Martial Which Tried, and the Orders of General Jackson for Shooting the Six Militia Men, 1828 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- O’Flaherty, Liam. Joseph Conrad---An Appreciation, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Oldham, W.S. Speech on the Resolutions of the State of Texas, 1865 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Oldham, W.S. Speech on the Subject of Finances, 1863 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Oldham, W.S. Speech upon the Bill to Amend the Conscript Law, 1862 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- O’Neill, John P., ed. Historic American Buildings Survey, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Organization of the Army of the Cumberland and of the Army of Tennessee, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Otis, Ephraim. The Nashville Campaign, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Paine, Thomas. Dissertation on First Principles of Government, Third Year of the French Republic, (1795). (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Parson Brownlow and The Unionists of East Tennessee, 1864; (2 copies) (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Paxton, A.G. The Atlanta Campaign, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Personne (F.G. de Fontaine). Army Letters, 1861-1865, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Petersburg National Military Park, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Pierson, H.W. A Letter to the Hon. Charles Sumner, 1870 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Pittsburg Landing and the Investment of Corinth, 1862 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Poe, Edgar Allen. Some Letters of Edgar Allen Poe to E.H.N. Patterson of Oquawka, Illinois, with comments by Eugene Field, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Poe, Edgar Allen. Tamerlane, 1827; (Facsimile printed in 1931) (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Poet Laureate of the Blue Bird Club. The Excursion of 4th July, 1860: A Heroic Poem (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Point Park, Lookout Mountain and Chattanooga Battlefields, 1950; (2 copies) (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Preston, Robert L. Southern Miscellanies, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- The Principles and Acts of Mr. Adams’ Administration, 1828 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Public Library of Nashville and Davidson County (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Purdue, Ida Pace. Papers Pertaining to the Confederacy, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Quandary, Christopher. Some Serious Considerations on the Present State of Parties, with Regard to the Presidential Election, 1827 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Randolph, W. F. (Captain of Jackson’s Bodyguard). With Stonewall Jackson at Chancellorsville (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Raynal, Abbe. The Revolution in America, 1782 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Rebel Pirate Shenandoah. Message from the President of the United States, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Reid, S.E. A History of Chester County, Tennessee, 1922; (Facsimile printed 1967) (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Rice, DeLong. The Story of Shiloh, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Richmond Battlefields, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Richmond National Battlefield Park, Fort Harrison, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Roads (Natchez Trace), 1934 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Roane Monument Unveiling, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Robert E. Lee, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Robert E. Lee---Soldier, Patriot, Educator, 1921; (2 copies) (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Robison, Mike. The Scar, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Rogers, E. G. Early Folk Medical Practices in Tennessee, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Rogers, Joseph W. Ghosts---What Was the Bell Witch?, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Rosters---Delegates to the M.M. Convention (a Confederate Veterans Reunion), 1910 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- The Round Table (A Dining Club of Twenty Gentlemen, Nashville 1884-1946) (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 5. Roush, J. Fred. Chalmette National Historical Park, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Ruskin, Gertrude McDaris. John Ross, Chief of an Eagle Race, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Rutherford, Mildred Lewis. Henry Wirz and the Andersonville Prison, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Rutherford, Mildred Lewis. Miss Rutherford’s Scrap Book, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Rutherford, Mildred Lewis. Miss Rutherford’s Historical Notes, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Rutherford, Mildred Lewis. Truths of History, n.d.; (2 copies) (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Rywell, Martin. Confederate Guns and Their Current Prices, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Sadler, Elizabeth Hatcher. The Bloom of Monticello, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- St. George’s Church (Nashville), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Sam Davis Home Chapter, United Daughters of the Confederacy. Son of the House---a Pageant, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Samson, Jonas D., et al. The Industries of Nashville, 1887 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Sanborn, Herbert. Methodology and the Monkey States, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- School Directors, 10th Civil District of Davidson County, Tennessee. An Open Reply to the Charges Made by the Investigating Committee Against the School Directors, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Scott, Valerie McNair (Lady Pakenham). Major-General Sir Edward M. Pakenham, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Sears, Claudius Wistar. Diary of C.W. Sears, n.d.; (typewritten copy of a diary dated from April, 1863-January, 1864) (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Sever, Catherine Elliott. After Sundown---A Memory of the South, 1957; (from an original ms. dated 1880) (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Shaw, Fred. Fred Shaw’s Dime American Songster, n.d.; (2 copies) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Shea, George. Jefferson Davis: A Statement Concerning the Imputed Special Causes of His Long Imprisonment …, 1877 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Shiloh National Military Park, Tennessee, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Significance of the Battle of Horseshoe Bend, Alabama, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Sigaud, Louis A. When Belle Boyd Wrote Lincoln, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Sioussat, St. George L. Andrew Johnson and the Early Phases of the Homestead Bill, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Slidell, John. Speech on the Neutrality Laws, 1858 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Smith, C. Alphonso. O. Henry (William Sidney Porter), 1921 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Smith, Daniel. A Short Description of the Tennessee Government, 1793; (a 1962 reprint of the original) (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Smith, H.H. J.E.B. Stuart, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Smith. H.H. Jefferson Davis (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Smith, H.H. Robert E. Lee, n.d.; (2 copies) (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Smith, Henry Louis. Lee the Educator, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- A Southron. South Carolina in the Revolutionary War, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Stanley, Theodora P. Fallacy of Gravitation, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Steel, S.A. The Tale of a School in the Sticks, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Antietam Campaign, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Battle of Chancellorsville, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Battle of Spottsylvania, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Battles Around Chattanooga, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Battles of the Wilderness, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Campaign of Atlanta, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Campaign of Fredericksburg, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Campaign of Koniggratz, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. Campaign of Scott in Mexico, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Campaign of Vicksburg, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Capture of Forts Henry and Donelson, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Chickamauga Campaign, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The First Battle of Bull Run, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Franco-German War---Campaign of Metz, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Franco-German War---Campaign of Sedan, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Gettysburg Campaign, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Invasions of Canada, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. Jackson’s Valley Campaign, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Mexican War---Taylor’s Campaign, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Peninsular Campaign, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. Revolutionary War, Northern Campaign, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. Revolutionary War, Southern Campaign, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Second Bull Run, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. Shiloh Campaign, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Siege of Petersburg, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The South African War, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Stone River Campaign, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Turko-Russian War, 1877-78---The Campaign of the Balkans, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The Turko-Russian War, 1877-78---The Siege of Plevna, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The War between Russia and Japan---First Period, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The War between Russia and Japan---Second Period, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Steele, Matthew F. Capt. The War of, 1812-1905 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Stephens, A.H. Speech on the Neutality Laws and the Arrest of General Walker by Commodore Paulding, 1858 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Stephens, William H. Tennessee; and the Duty of her Educated Sons, 1871 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Stevens, Robley D. Autograph Collection Guide, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Stokes, Nellie Treanor. Rachel Jackson, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Storrick, C.W. The Battle of Gettysburg, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- The Story of the Tennessee Capitol, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Stout, L.H. Reminiscences of General Braxton Bragg, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Stratford Hall Plantation, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Sumner County Library Board. A Short History of Sumner, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Sweeny, Talbot. A Vindication of Robert E. Lee, 1890 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Synon, John J. Our Times, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Tannehill, Wilkins. Address Delivered to Cumberland Lodge, 1819 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Tansill, Robert. Free and Impartial Exposition of the Causes Which Led to the Failure of the Confederate States to Establish Their Independence, 1865 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Tapp, Hambleton. The Battle of Perryville, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Tarkington, Booth. The Spring Concert, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Taylor, George. Speech on the Clayton-Bulwer Treaty, 1858 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Taylor, George L. Governor Taylor’s Love Letters to the Public, 1899 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Tennessee Centennial and International Exposition, 1896 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Tennessee Highways, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Tennessee Historical Society. The Charter and By-Laws of the Tennessee Historical Society, 1878; (2 copies) (Box 18, Folder 34)
- The Tennessee Scene---Camera Impressions, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Tennessee’s Sesquicentennial Exhibition at the Library of Congress, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Third National Bank. Nashville, 1927-1952, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Thomasson, William. The Glacial Period and the Deluge, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Thompson, J.J. Kentucky Tragedy---The Hill and Evans Feud, 1854 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Thompson, Ray. The Confederate Shrine at Beauvoir, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Tilford, T.G. Common Sense and Integration, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Tilley, John S. Facts the Historians Leave Out, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Travelers Rest Arabian Horses, Franklin, Tennessee, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Turley, William T. (Aged Thirteen Years) Glittering Dew Drops; A Poetical Work, 1871 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Turner, Justin G. The Mary Lincoln Letters to Mrs. Felician Slataper, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Twain, Mark. Date…1601---Conversation as It Was by the Social Fireside in the Time of the Tudors, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Twain, Mark. To the Person Sitting in Darkness and Concerning the Rev. Mr. Ament, 1926 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Tyler, Lyon Gardiner. A Confederate Catechism, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Tyler, Lyon Gardiner. General Lee’s Birthday, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- The United States and England---Being a Reply to the Criticism on Inchiquin’s Letters, 1814 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- University of Oklahoma Press---1953 Spring Books (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Vail, R.W.G. The Ulster County Gazette and Its Illegitimate Offspring, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Van Zandt, Franklin K. Boundaries of the United States and the Several States, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Vincent, Bert. Us Mountain Folks, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Vincent, Bert. Here in Tennessee, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- The Virginia Battlefields Tour from Manassas to Appomattox, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Visit Colonial Williamsburg with Us, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Wade, Herbert Treadwell. A Brief History of the Colonial Wars in America, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Walker, William. The Unity of Art, 1848; (2 copies) (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Walton, Sarah L. Memories of Rugby Colony, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Ward, Mrs. George R. Testimony before United States Senate Committee on Relations Between Labor and Capital, 1883 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Washington and Tusculum College. Charter and By-Laws, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Watson, Elbert L. Tennessee at the Battle of New Orleans, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Welburn, Drummond. Select Poems, 1895 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Wells, Gabriel. The Carter-Pollard Disclosures, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Weiss, Harry B. Concerning the Activities of Charles F. Heartman, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- The Logistics of Nathan Bedford Forrest, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Wharton, T.A. Rev. General Robert E. Lee, the Man, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Wheelock, Mrs. W.E. (Amenda Neal) Rhea Springs (Box 20, Folder 12)
- White, E.V. The First Iron-Clad Engagement in the World, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Whitehill, Walter Muir. The Many Faces of Monticello, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Wiley, J.W. St Mary’s Church, Jackson, Tennessee, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Williams, Samuel C. The Admission of Tennessee into the Union, 1945; (2 copies) (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Williams, Samuel C. History of Johnson City and Its Environs, 1940; (2 copies) (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Williams, Samuel C. William Tatham, Wataugan, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Wills, Jesse E. Meditations on the American Indian, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Wilson, John Lyde. The Code of Honor; or Rules for the Government of Principals and Seconds in Duelling, 1858 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Wilson, Samuel, Jr. Plantation Houses in the Battle of New Orleans, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Winsor, Justin. Was Shakespeare Shapleigh?, 1887 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Wirt, Alvin. The Upper Cumberland in Pioneer Times, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Wise, Jennings C. MacArthur Saga, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Wise, John S. Southern Soldiers and V.M.I. Cadets, Who Fell in the Battle of New Market, ca., 1898 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Womack, J.J. The Civil War Diary of J.J. Womack, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Woman’s Division of Christian Service of the Methodist Church. A Charter of Racial Policies, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Woods, Fayla. History of Davidson County, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Worthington, T. Shiloh: the Only Correct Military History of U.S. Grant and of the Missing Army Records for Which He Alone Is Responsible to Conceal His Organized Defeat of the Union Army at Shiloh, 1872 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Young, Bennett H. The South in History, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Young, Bernice Fearn. Howard Weeden---A Rose of Yesterday, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Young, L.D. Reminiscences of a Soldier in the Orphan Brigade, ca., 1917 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Your Guide to the Fort Donelson Historical Tour, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 12)